릴리언에이
and also Park Yoon Woo
descendant of muldu
all names and events are fictitious
any coincidences are random
drug use is a crime
which entails the destruction of personality
and also negatively affects your 7 and the environment
banned substances in south korea
they are difficult to import and difficult to sell, delivery
why
at 1
Koreans are also moralists
2 Korean customs and police work flawlessly
yes
curse
come out
I warned you
I won't repeat it
oh you and you get out
the brute come over
let's go in
infection
90% of supplies are blocked by bingo
but the remaining 10 guarantee success
high risks
high earnings
your application has been rejected
notice of closure
be there
for the sake of this 10%
many are willing to take risks
for those who have lost everything
Prohibited substances can be a lucky ticket
I'll try
legen
watercolor painting
10 kilograms will be
and I
I'm different
it's all for me
like cards in a game
needed for something more
that's why I'm curious
what can this woman give me episode 2
I'll do it
I'm waiting tomorrow
even if it's only 15g
who are you and
this is
what are you talking about
why are you following me
do you remember me teacher
you are mom sua
I mean what is the fate of James
teacher you are James
don't get me wrong
I just came to see a friend
I want with you
that I'm with you
let's do business together
didn't think
that I will see the parents of students under such circumstances
I understand, I’m as surprised as you are
do you often visit medusa
no I wouldn't say
and you've been doing this for a long time
business where did you get this
This is the first time I've seen this
Well, be sure to talk about it
I don't work with that
what I don't understand
your business is not you 1 want to buy it who you are
tell me
in this area it is necessary
carefully select partners
I have to believe you
teacher you forgot what I saw
so what now
what if I don't fall for it
what will you do
tell me
that a diligent teacher does something illegal at night
why not
maybe you can tell me everything sua
what does her mom do?
remember ka
taking advantage of other people's weaknesses
you yourself will become weak
sit down it's business
we will sign a contract with you
means
we are partners
tell me honestly
you came here
you think that I'll beat you up a little and let you go
stop
Sonya so sir
then you knew
what were you going for
can you even imagine
what kind of substance is this
its level is different from everything that was before
it was brewed specifically for VIPs
crystal clear
and the idiot from your gang stole it from us
if only you had a little sense of responsibility
you would have found him
these are basic rules of decency
It's not like you're a fool
must think
after all, it was you who told the stupid Panama to take the goods
so what is our fault shut up
그
그 그
partnership agreement
this agreement between James A and Kang Insu B
are installed
Binding rights and obligations
when supplied with excess methamphetamine
what is it why we stopped
something doesn't suit you
1 kan insu undertakes to supply the goods
if
the contents of paragraph 1 will become known to anyone without consent
and the partnership will end
in case
violations by partner b 2 points
or if a suffers losses due to the fault of b
partner b is obliged to compensate for damage
if problems arise
related to the supply of goods
b is obliged to solve it and compensate for losses
continue
between a and b the profit ratio is 7-3
that's ok
yes
what's wrong with that
you can sit quietly on your sofa at home
and I need to look for new sales outlets and communicate with clients
I have conditions
if I can be more useful
we will reconsider the conditions
how interesting
Let's see how useful you will be
let's move on
by the way
what is the name of your product
How is it different from regular ice?
mint
what
shaped like mint candies
I'm just curious
why do you need this
you're clearly a newbie
you're shaking with fear
oh well
I don't quite understand
what's going on
but I'm having fun
you don't have to understand
here you go
yes
I did it
I
agreed
dong hyun
oh yeah
I'll finish you off
dong hyun
how come
Jun hyung
if you don't find the bag
next time
I will cut off your dong hyun's arms and legs
did you understand me
yes or no
I understand you
woojin was born in december 90 6
daughter of the president of V Entertainment
Mimi Yumison was born in October 90 6 influencer
Hansung Jae was born in June 90 6
nephew for the Minister of Justice
government subsidies for tu en bio
creation of a network of companies
the center of which will be that en
Kan Khverim was born in July 90 2
Mimi's 16th 0th birthday VIPs will come
wrestling department
with drugs in Gwangnam area
organized a search for a bag containing 10kg of methamphetamine
10kg is enough
to hook 300,000 people
also known as phantom phantom
looks like ice
where did it get its name from
lost batch
if you hurry
problems will arise
form and composition
of course they are different
but time 1
courier
the subscriber's device is turned off or is outside
network coverage areas
oh damn
no wait dong hyun
joon hyung you promised
dong hyun no need
hey
let me go let me go
it hurts a lot
I'll live for now
treatment should have started earlier
I'm sorry
for everything
remember
when
we just got married
you brought stray animals into your house
and they all needed help
and you
I didn't even know you were allergic to them
I sneezed and walked around with a runny nose every day
assuring everyone that it’s a cold
when I was sad
I kept thinking
maybe you're on me too
married out of pity
in your eyes I'm helpless
because my parents died and it's hard for me
no
you're cool
you looked so confident
even being lonely
that's why I married you
I hope I stay like this
in your eyes
whatever I do
of course
you're doing everything right
I wish it were like this now
you know where you ended up
Mimi happy birthday to you
let's take a photo
see all
we're at mimi's birthday party
it's so cool here
convey your congratulations
thanks everyone for coming
let's start with the most important
enough already sanji it's fun
are you here james
meet today
he tried his best for us
let's really clap
strangers this is Sung Jae's nephew
Deputy Minister of Justice
this is hverim
kan hverim
hey hey hey what the heck
no phones
our lord kan will be angry
and so on every time
be careful with him
you were appointed director
need to be more careful
already director
You haven’t even worked for 2 years
so this is his company
tell him to curry favor
hey james
you too
come on already
are you james
we finally met in person, I’ve heard a lot about you, I’m curious
wait a minute
you know each other
I heard you are friends
We've been friends with him since childhood
next time be more careful
of course
and there are guys like you
who are literally winged by flattery
but you went too far
I can’t even give a business card to anyone now
overall everything is good
but the problem is with the guests
it's as easy as shelling pears
hey hey, did you decide to start a showdown at her birthday?
I don't mind, arrange this for me too
just to make it epic
he's not even in charge
a gift from the heart
my god it's the same
I can't believe it
best gift in history
cash register
yes you had dinner
Yes, we ate puli kogi with jinha
see you in the morning love you
and I you
what am I doing
detective yes
we've been here for several days and nothing
look here we searched the whole henbok area and nothing
we must be consistent
and you're too risky
I’ve already buzzed the kids from the area all their ears
so that they could immediately inform me about the security guards of the clubs
exactly
weren't you the one who wrote the explanatory note for that?
that someone reported on you
they say you all
customers were scared away
yes I wrote
eat your hamburger
it's just amazing there
how cool it was thank you
let's get together
just like that right away
아
I'll sort it out
what the heck is he?
you give it to everyone
what ah
you're an idiot
completely crazy
what about
Mimi
hey let's go
where did you go
I don't want to let me go
the bastards wanted to die
and you too or something
for me you died today
listen
you know what
there are people who talk more
But there are those who, on the contrary, act like me
you're really sick
I'm Irim's best friend
you think you can get away with it
cowardly freak
stuck in your fantasies
your friendship doesn't give you any power over him
If you understand, then get lost and don’t come into my sight again
how dare he yes how dare he
useless trash
아이
아
하
what hatched
cleaning lady
it's all because of you
I spent so much money on a room
but because of you I lost everything
don't come closer
well try it
come on
I feel lousy and want revenge
I'll do it
woman you are absolutely oh you
listen to me too
ruined my mood
on
see this get out of here shoot
let's go
you're a sneaky cowardly bastard
crazy
I've gone completely crazy
wow
I finally cursed
what's wrong with him
looks like an accident
man inside
he's injured, call the police quickly
or an ambulance please
wait now
hello hello there's a person here
well
Mimi
don't be sour
there are such people
I heard something coming at me and was inspired
as they say there
kindness above all
right, another important thing
my new friend wouldn't do that
like mint again
it's mint yes
that's what he's getting off of
not bad
really good really good
incredible where did you get it
for how many sales
name any price
I think we know each other
don't know me
fix it and we can take it away
please
alive yes
we carry only carefully
he's probably pushing sleeping pills, you drink them
be careful with your words
sorry sorry
sorry strong guy yes
let's move on
you're talking about a familiar face
I wish it were true
you're pretty
where are you really from?
it was always interesting
as if not from Korea
study abroad
although no
everyone knows each other there
oh my god
or you
kept man
sounds like the truth
yes I know everyone there
she's right to us
or itaewon yeah tell me
so okay
you can take your time
while we have a little drink
yes we drink we drink
it's my birthday
1 more
exactly the same as in the motel near the kimpongnam
where did he crawl from?
and yes this is the case here
We didn’t see this, let’s look at the cameras
Is it a teacher?
teacher
here
what are you pushing?
who's pushing there
is the teacher here?
and that there is a warrant
you know what this is hey let me know
this means that a warrant is not needed here, skip it
hey no we can't
skip it
teacher
here I am
legen legen
teacher
here
what was James looking at?
the police are here
let's go to the 2nd floor
yeah eh
really cool let's go to the 2nd floor
why are you up?
hi are you already open?
I'll rent your bar, I guarantee
high sales
just clear the tables
hey let me explain hey hey
you see me leave quickly
all on the 2nd floor
wait for me
it's the police, disperse
listen attention attention wait stop
give way
I ask everyone to disperse
everyone should leave
go your separate ways
give way
start with the CCTV camera I obey
what are you talking about
oh damn
turn off the cameras
looking at the stairs and 3rd room
good
don't touch anything
narcotics department
we want to check the cameras
what's there
walking along the corridor with VIP rooms
they enter room 3
man wait a minute not interested
yes yes they went that way
what happened
oh sorry the wire got caught
damn
what
exactly this room
where did everyone go, let's look further
Room 3 let's look there
room 3
driving is a danger
that's why i can't
힘껏 소리쳐
나도 상처 났어
let's go
what a waste
what's going on
we don't do that kind of stuff here
heard gossip somewhere and ruined your weekend
and what do you want me to do
from loss of profit
I'll file a lawsuit against you, got it?
the head of the camera flew off
Well, how do you like 1 deal?
a
how do you do things
those people are your clients
yes
you thought I would play mother's daughter with them
no need to be afraid
Koreans are strange people
there are so many bad things in the world
and they are afraid of some substances
like it's a contagious disease
isn't it?
Dear, what do you think?
what crimes are there more
committed by drunkards or drug addicts
Am I speculating in real estate?
come to think of it
this is much worse
it harms the whole country
but this doesn't harm anyone
doesn't force anyone
they just like it and that's it
just try
Why don’t you accept it yourself then?
I mean everyone was treated to champagne with mint
and you haven’t even tried it yourself
and you turn out to be big-eyed
Well, yes, I’ve stopped sticking my nose where they don’t ask
and just take the money
ok
우와
하
I divided the profits as we agreed
but today you helped me
this is a token of gratitude
and in the future, don’t bother with personal questions
got it
I'll go
stand
what more will you bring next time
clients liked it
it will take a lot more
or immediately give everything you have
teacher, do you have enough money?
how much is left
kilogram
quite a lot
I'll think about it
courier
to leave a voice message press 1
This is me, let's go offline for now
everything is fine
everything's ok
I'm sorry
thank you
5,000,000 won
more than I earned in the store in 3 months
and so on every day
already arrived
go back to sleep
you cried
no
yeah I didn't cry
it means it's a nightmare
all from behind the couch
don't sleep in the hospital
not at all
I had a good dream
wonderful
I cried with happiness
stupid
good dreams bring smiles, not tears
right
this is the sample
which you were talking about
something I'm not sure
I should check
are you kidding if you
see my face it's over
앉아셋
worse than a dog
what happens if you find a thief
what about you
don't know
good
then wait
ahh
where are you talking
the bag is missing
this is for the treatment of pacto gin
ok just a minute
kang insoo
phantom
where did you get this
1st time I see this
but be sure to talk about it
I don't work with that
what I don't understand
here you come
Let's all welcome our fugitive together
today we will practice colors
get ready well
changed brushes
be stunned
how expensive
great and updated the colors
wow, how did you spend so much?
look at the new colors
what's there
go crazy
what colors I want too
I've never even seen anything like this
and I'm beautiful
they are real
stop looking at other people's colors
better prepare yours well
don't worry about anything, daughter, I love you
well, you collected everything yes
what's wrong with your finger
you can deliver everything
Well, I cut my finger
what will you do
with someone who stole the goods
I'll kill
you'll kill
where are you talking
the bag is missing
happy street I'll check
descendant of muldu
you know
how did I survive here
I don't need you
I just want to know
who brought the drugs
I never take risks
I'll do everything
then bring everything
what did you steal
My husband's treatment and mortgage payment costs 186,000,000
that's all I need to worry about
if you listen
I will save your life
let's die together teacher